Guide to the Alvin A. Achenbaum Papers, 1948-2011 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Achenbaum Bogda Associates, 1971-2009 and undated
  - Account Files
    - Neostem
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2007-2008 (Box AB31)
      - Printed material, 2007 and undated (Box AB31)
      - Stem cell reports, 2007 (Box AB31)
    - Omnipoint
      - Competitrack reports, 1997 (Box AB31)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1996-1999, (2 folders) (Box AB32)
      - Designor System, 1998 (Box AB32)
      - Direct advertising, 1996-1998 (Box AB32)
      - Tracking study, 1998 (Box AB32)
    - Pfizer/Warner-Lambert
      - Agency management meetings, 1998 (Box AB32)
      - Background of merger, 2001 (Box AB32)
      - Comparison of Carat and Mindshare, 2000 (Box AB32)
      - Compensation, 2000 (Box AB32)
      - Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box AB32)
      - Fees, 2000 (Box AB32)
      - Media agency review, 1998-2000, (4 folders) (Box AB32)
      - Media AOR review final meetings, 2000 (Box AB33)
      - Media compensation agreement, 1998-1999 (Box AB33)
      - Merger, 2000 (Box AB33)
      - Paragon Media, 1998 (Box AB33)
    - RARE Hospitality
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2004 (Box AB33)
    - Ryerson Tull
      - ABA presentation, undated (Box AB33)
      - Achieving Profitable Growth--Chicago/Great Lakes, 2002, (2 folders) (Box AB33)
      - Achieving Profitable Growth--Market Situation Analysis, 2002 (Box AB33)
      - Agency position papers, 2002 (Box AB33)
      - Agency relationship services--competition listing, 2003 (Box AB33)
      - Agency search, 2002 (Box AB34)
      - Aluminum, 2003, (2 folders) (Box AB34)
      - Annual report, 1999-2005, (4 folders) (Box AB34)
      - Appendix, undated (Box AB34)
      - April 4 meeting, 2002 (Box AB34)
      - April 9 Chicago meeting, 2003 (Box AB34)
      - April 10 meeting, 2002 (Box AB34)
      - Big 5 Growth Roadmap, 2003 (Box AB34)
      - Big Brothers and Big Sisters, 2004 (Box AB34)
      - Bottom-top survey data, 2001 (Box AB34)
      - Brand assets, undated (Box AB34)
      - Branding articles, 1997-2002 (Box AB35)
      - Buffalo meeting, undated (Box AB35)
      - Building profitable sales, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Business relationships survey, 2001 (Box AB35)
      - Business to business presentation, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Case history, 2004 (Box AB35)
      - Chicago kick-off meeting, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Chicago OSR survey, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Chicago sales meeting, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Coil processing research, 2002 (Box AB35)
      - Cold-drawn bars, 2003 (Box AB35)
      - Communications plan, 2003 (Box AB35)
      - Compensation review, 2003 (Box AB35)
      - Competitive positioning and brand reputation, 2001 (Box AB36)
      - Conclusions/recommendations, 2002 (Box AB36)
      - Current projects, 2003 (Box AB36)
      - Customer interviews, 2002 (Box AB36)
      - Customer/product roadmap, 2003 (Box AB36)
      - Customer promotion, 2003 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB36)
      - Customer research, 2002-2005 and undated, (3 folders) (Box AB36)
      - Customer satisfaction, 2002, (2 folders) (Box AB36)
      - Customer survey, 2001-2003, (2 folders) (Box AB36)
      - Customer Value Focus Team, 2000-2001, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box AB36)
      - Customer Value Focus Team, 2000-2001, (3 of 3 folders) (Box AB37)
      - Developing a Process to Implement Competitive Market Pricing, 2002 (Box AB37)
      - Direct mailing, undated (Box AB37)
      - Direct marketing, 2001 (Box AB37)
      - Distribution, 202 (Box AB37)
      - Draft of strategic and tactical recommendation, 2002 (Box AB37)
      - Employee survey (Hewitt), 2004 (Box AB37)
      - Factor analysis, 2001 (Box AB37)
      - Fast Path program, 2002-2003, (6 folders) (Box AB37)
      - Gary Niederpruem breakfast meeting, 2003 (Box AB37)
      - Generating Profitable Revenue in a Changing Market Environment, 2002 (Box AB38)
      - Gibson & Associates, 2001 (Box AB38)
      - Growth--An Imperative, 2002 (Box AB38)
      - Growth model, 2002 (Box AB38)
      - Implications of Price Competition on Brands, Advertising and the Economy, 1992 (Box AB38)
      - Improving the Bottom Line, undated (Box AB38)
      - Interview guide, 2001-2002 (Box AB38)
      - Journey to Profitable Growth, 2003 (Box AB38)
      - J. P. Morgan research, 2003 (Box AB38)
      - Key performance indicators, 2000-2002, (3 folders) (Box AB38)
      - Keys to Generating Profitable Revenue Growth, undated (Box AB38)
      - Leadership conference, 2002 (Box AB38)
      - Leadership meeting, 2002-2003, (3 folders) (Box AB38)
      - Letter of commendation, 2005 (Box AB38)
      - Macro Assessment (Bourton Group), 2002 (Box AB39)
      - Marketing budget, 2002 (Box AB39)
      - Marketing Communications Tools, 2002 (Box AB39)
      - Marketing growth programs, 2003 (Box AB39)
      - Marketing meetings, 2003, (5 folders) (Box AB39)
      - Marketing migration to South and West, 2003 (Box AB39)
      - Marketing planning outline, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - Marketing situation analysis, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - McKinsey proposal, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - Meeting responses, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - Merger with Integris, 2005, (2 folders) (Box AB40)
      - Metal research recommendations, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - Metals report, undated (Box AB40)
      - Monthly reports, 2001 (Box AB40)
      - Ned's strategic plans, 2002 (Box AB40)
      - Needs Based Segmentation, 2000 (Box AB40)
      - Niederpruem, 2004 (Box AB40)
      - NOP telephone study, 2001 (Box AB40)
      - Notes for report, 2002 (Box AB41)
      - Objectives, 2002 (Box AB41)
      - Patti Mosbrooker/Gary Niederpruem meeting, 2003 (Box AB41)
      - Plate A36 mill edge, 2003 (Box AB41)
      - Presentations, 2002 (Box AB41)
      - Price analysis, 2003 (Box AB41)
      - Price matrix, 2003 (Box AB41)
      - Price survey, 2003 (Box AB41)
      - Pricing presentation, 2003 and undated (Box AB41)
      - Pricing process, undated (Box AB41)
      - Pricing reports, 2003 and undated (Box AB42)
      - Pricing RT/Integris merger, 2005 (Box AB42)
      - Pricing strategy, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Pricing study, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Priorities, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Procedures, 2001 and undated (Box AB42)
      - Product literature, 1990-2001 and undated (Box AB42)
      - Product management, 2002-2003 (Box AB42)
      - Product offerings, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Product Roadmap to Growth, 2002-2003, (2 folders) (Box AB42)
      - Products and plans, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Profitable Revenue Growth Project, 2002 (Box AB42)
      - Project status, 2002-2003 (Box AB43)
      - Projects and schedules, 2005 (Box AB43)
      - Prologue--The Challenge Facing RT, 2002 (Box AB43)
      - Promotion letters, 2002 (Box AB43)
      - Proposal for customer retention (Savo Group), 2002 (Box AB43)
      - Quarterly reports, 2001-2002, (2 folders) (Box AB43)
      - Recommendation, 2002 (Box AB43)
      - Regional data, 2001-2002, (1-4 of 6 folders) (Box AB43)
      - Regional data, 2001-2003, (5-6 of 5 folders) (Box AB44)
      - Reliance Steel and Aluminum, 2001 (Box AB44)
      - Reports, 2002-2005, (2 folders) (Box AB44)
      - Research, 2000-2002, (4 folders) (Box AB44)
      - Response to Questions about the Corporate Strategic Marketing Plan Proposal, undated (Box AB44)
      - Road Map, 2003 (Box AB44)
      - Roper data, 2003 (Box AB44)
      - RT/Integris proposal, 2005 (Box AB45)
      - Sales aids, 2003 (Box AB45)
      - Sales call tracking, 2001 (Box AB45)
      - Sales force, 2002 (Box AB45)
      - Sales incentive plan, 2003 (Box AB45)
      - Sales tool planning, 2003 (Box AB45)
      - Segmentation and satisfaction, 2001 (Box AB45)
      - Selecting an Advertising and Public Relations Agency, 2002 (Box AB45)
      - Service Center costs, 2003 (Box AB45)
      - Service Center market shares, 2002 (Box AB45)
      - Situation analysis--Chicago/Great Lakes/Atlantic regions, 2002 (Box AB45)
      - Stainless steel, 2002, (2 folders) (Box AB45)
      - Steel market outlook, 2001 (Box AB45)
      - Stock list, 1995 (Box AB45)
      - Straight line steel, 2001 (Box AB45)
      - Strategic recommendation, undated (Box AB45)
      - Stress Testing the Corporate Strategy, 2002 (Box AB45)
      - Stress Testing the Corporate Strategy, 2002 (Box AB46)
      - Summary of ABA Strategic Hierarchy Model, undated (Box AB46)
      - The Customer, undated (Box AB46)
      - Tritech, 2002 (Box AB46)
      - Vision statements, 2001-2002 (Box AB46)
      - Weekly update meetings, 2002 (Box AB46)
    - Service Corp.
      - Agency selection, 2004 (Box AB46)
    - Snap-On Tools
      - Challenge Holdings--China market study, 1996, (3 folders) (Box AB46)
    - State of Florida Attorney General Office
      - Continental Consulting Group, 2003 (Box AB46)
      - EBJ International Consultants, 2003 (Box AB46)
      - Mercer Island Group, 2003, (2 folders) (Box AB46)
      - RCG (Rojek Cutcher Group), 2003, (2 folders) (Box AB46)
    - Subaru
      - ABA presentation, 2004 (Box AB46)
    - Texas Instruments
      - Agency search, undated (Box AB46)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2004 (Box AB46)
    - Unisys
      - Agency review, 2000, (2 folders) (Box AB47)
      - Compensation agreement with Grey Worldwide, 2000-2001 (Box AB47)
    - United Auto Group
      - Bridgestone/Firestone Retailing Opportunity, circa 1996 (Box AB47)
      - Goodyear Retailing Opportunity, circa 1996 (Box AB47)
      - Merrill Lynch report, circa 1996 (Box AB47)
      - Sears presentation, 1996, (2 folders) (Box AB47)
      - Wal-Mart Retailing Opportunity, 1996 (Box AB47)
    - Wallpaper Council
      - Agency search, 1997, (1-2 of 4 folders) (Box AB47)
      - Agency search, 1997, (3-4 of 4 folders) (Box AB48)
      - Amster-Young
        - Billing, 1999 (Box AB48)
        - Chris Madden (spokesperson), 1999 (Box AB48)
        - Contracts, 1998 (Box AB48)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998-1999, (5 folders) (Box AB48)
        - Invoices, 1998-1999 (Box AB49)
        - Meeting agenda, 1998 (Box AB49)
        - PR account review, 1999 (Box AB49)
      - Better Homes & Gardens research, 1999 (Box AB49)
      - Billing, 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box AB49)
      - Board meeting, 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box AB49)
      - Budget and finance, 1998-1999, (1-3 of 6 folders) (Box AB49)
      - Budget and finance, 1998-1999, (4-6 of 6 folders) (Box AB50)
      - Bylaws, undated (Box AB50)
      - Clippings and media, 1997-1998, (3 folders) (Box AB50)
      - Contract, 1999-2000 (Box AB50)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1997-1999, (4 folders) (Box AB50)
      - Executive Committee meeting, 1997-1998 (Box AB50)
      - Industry printed material, 1997-1999 (Box AB51)
      - Media inserts, 1997-1998 (Box AB51)
      - notes, undated (Box AB51)
      - PSK (Pagano Schenck & Kay)
        - Agency compensation, 1997 and undated (Box AB51)
        - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1998-1999 (Box AB51)
        - Invoices, 1997-1999 (Box AB51)
        - Media, 1999, (2 folders) (Box AB51)
        - Media plan, 1997 (Box AB51)
        - Media recommendation, 2000 (Box AB51)
        - Research, 1998 (Box AB51)
      - Paint and Decorating Retailer, 1998 (Box AB51)
      - Research, 1998 (Box AB52)
      - Retail policy, 1998 (Box AB52)
    - Western Union/First Data
      - Agency review, undated (Box AB52)
      - Agency search, 2002-2004 (Box AB52)
      - Fact sheet responses, 2002 (Box AB52)
      - Finalist meetings, 2002 (Box AB52)
      - Request for position papers, undated (Box AB52)
      - Revenue data, 2000 (Box AB52)
    - Zoigo
      - Internet platform, 2009 (Box AB52)
  - General Files
    - 4-A's overhead compensation, 2000-2003 (Box AB52)
    - Achenbaum's Agency Search Secrets, undated (Box AB52)
    - Advertising expenditures, 1986-2002, (2 folders) (Box AB52)
    - Agency assignments, 1994-1997 (Box AB52)
    - Agency compensation audit instructions, 1989 and undated (Box AB52)
    - Agency compensation notes, 1986-1998 (Box AB52)
    - Agency Relationship Marketing Plan, 1998 (Box AB53)
    - Agency Research Council, 2004 (Box AB53)
    - Agency Review funnel diagram, undated (Box AB53)
    - Agency reviews, 1997-1998 (Box AB53)
    - Agency Search, Compensation and Relationship Services, circa 2000 (Box AB53)
    - Agency search criteria, circa 2007 (Box AB53)
    - Agency search document binder, 1977-2002, (2 folders) (Box AB53)
    - Agency search process, 1997 (Box AB53)
    - Agency search proposals, 1993 and undated (Box AB53)
    - ANA meetings, 2002-2004 (Box AB53)
    - Annual assessment formats, 1983-1997 (Box AB53)
    - Assignments, undated (Box AB53)
    - Atlanta conference, 1999 (Box AB53)
    - Backgrounder/fact sheet, undated (Box AB53)
    - Bill Griffith presentation, 2000 (Box AB53)
    - Biographies
      - Alvin Achenbaum, undated (Box AB53)
      - Joel Baumwoll, undated (Box AB53)
      - Peter Bogda, undated (Box AB53)
    - Brand Asset Based Strategic Marketing Planning, undated, (2 folders) (Box AB54)
    - Brochures, undated (Box AB54)
    - Business of Getting New Business, undated (Box AB54)
    - Choosing and Compensating an Advertising Agency (leave-behind packet), undated (Box AB54)
    - Client recommendations and testimonials, 1977-2004, (2 folders) (Box AB54)
    - Client views of marketing, 1992-1995 and undated (Box AB54)
    - Clippings and media, 1995-2005 and undated, (2 folders) (Box AB54)
    - Competitive Brand Asset Performance Assessment, undated (Box AB54)
    - Competitors, 2003 (Box AB54)
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1994-2003 (Box AB55)
    - Credentials presentation, 2004 (Box AB55)
    - Dallas Advertising League panel questions, 2004 (Box AB55)
    - E-commerce, 1999 (Box AB55)
    - Edward Landquist, 1996-1997 and undated (Box AB55)
    - Generating Profitable Revenue in a Changing Market Environment, undated (Box AB55)
    - Health care concept, 1996 and undated (Box AB55)
    - Internet/interactive media, 1997-2000, (2 folders) (Box AB55)
    - Legal letters, 1995 (Box AB55)
    - Managing Brand Assets for Profitable Revenue Growth, 2000 (Box AB55)
    - Managing for Profitable Revenue Growth, 2000 (Box AB55)
    - Marketing Matters (column), 1997 (Box AB55)
    - Marketing planning presentation, undated (Box AB55)
    - Marketing Solution System for Increasing Profitable Revenue, undated (Box AB55)
    - Marketing Solutions for a Changing Environment, undated (Box AB55)
    - Maximizing Competitive Performance, undated (Box AB56)
    - Meeting the Changing Demands of a Marketing-Adverse Consumer (William Daddi), 2004 (Box AB56)
    - Meetings, 1993-1996 (Box AB56)
    - New business, 1988-2003 and undated, (4 folders) (Box AB56)
    - New business presentation, 2000 (Box AB56)
    - New business solicitations, 1993-2001, (2 folders) (Box AB56)
    - New business status presentation, undated (Box AB57)
    - Outlines for meetings with prospects, 2000 and undated (Box AB57)
    - Overview presentations, undated (Box AB57)
    - Planing meeting summary, undated (Box AB57)
    - Planning schematics, undated (Box AB57)
    - Presentation, undated (Box AB57)
    - Press contacts, 1997 (Box AB57)
    - Public relations program, undated (Box AB57)
    - Reasons for Selecting ABA and other reasons lists, undated (Box AB57)
    - Russian trip presentation--Nature of Marketing, 2001 (Box AB57)
    - Sample compensations agreement, 2003 (Box AB57)
    - Sample letters, 1998 and undated (Box AB57)
    - Skidmore College, 2004 (Box AB57)
    - Solicitation letters, 2004 (Box AB57)
    - Strategic Hierarchy, undated (Box AB57)
    - Take-away cards, undated (Box AB57)
    - Testimonial letters, 1977-2002 (Box AB57)
    - Thoughts on Advertising, 2003 (Box AB57)
    - Trademark law, 2000-2009 (Box AB57)
    - Traditional compensation structures, 1997-2001 (Box AB57)
    - Trends and Outlook (Robert Coen/McCann Erickson), 2000 (Box AB57)
- Achenbaum Institute of Marketing, 2005-2007 and undated
  - Asia information, 2007 (Box AM1)
  - Company name notes, 2005 (Box AM1)
  - Democrats in national elections, 2006-2007, (3 folders) (Box AM1)
  - Howard Dean proposal, 2006 (Box AM1)
  - Intellectual property notes, undated (Box AM1)
  - Logo and stationery designs, undated (Box AM1)
  - Printed materials, 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box AM1)
- Achenbaum Marketing Communications, 2003-2008 and undated
  - Account Files
    - Motor Coach Industries (MCI)
      - Business plan, 2006 (Box AM1)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 2006 (Box AM1)
      - Cover sheets, 2006 (Box AM1)
      - Growth plan, 2005 (Box AM2)
      - MCI fleet support parts list, 2005 (Box AM2)
      - Pricing report drafts, 2006 (Box AM2)
      - Pricing strategy, undated (Box AM2)
      - Pricing study, 2006, (2 folders) (Box AM2)
      - Sales data, 2003-2006, (2 folders) (Box AM2)
  - General Files
    - Corporate records, 2005 (Box AM2)
    - Corporate records binder (article of incorporation, bylaws, minutes, etc.), 2005 (Box AM3)
    - Financial, 2005-2008 (Box AM3)
    - Gary Wachter (production), 2004 (Box AM3)
    - Publicity/announcements, 2005 (Box AM3)
    - Retirement plan, 2005, (2 folders) (Box AM3)
- Backer Spielvogel Bates, 1971-1995 and undated
  - Account Files
    - Campbell Soup
      - Account review meeting, 1990 (Box BB1)
      - Agency compensation, 1986 (Box BB1)
      - Agency incentive program, 1990 (Box BB1)
      - Brand equity extension, 1990 (Box BB1)
      - BSB--The First 60 Days, undated (Box BB1)
      - BSB 1990-1991 revitalization plan, 1990 (Box BB1)
      - Campbell Soup 1994, 1989 (Box BB1)
      - Campbell's advertising seminar, 1991 (Box BB1)
      - Chicken Noodle, 1990 (Box BB1)
      - Children's project--Kids' Soup, 1992 (Box BB1)
      - Clippings, 1987-1991 (Box BB1)
      - Consumer Attitudes toward Health and Soup, undated (Box BB1)
      - Consumer panel purchase data, 1989 (Box BB1)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1986-1991, (2 folders) (Box BB1)
      - Eating Soup campaign, 1991 (Box BB2)
      - Florida food conference, 1991 (Box BB2)
      - Food advertising presentation, 1990 (Box BB2)
      - Food marketing meeting presentation, undated (Box BB2)
      - Food World of Children and the Campbell Soup Co., undated (Box BB2)
      - How Do We Grow?, 1988 (Box BB2)
      - Home Cookin' focus group, 1991 (Box BB2)
      - Improving promotion spending productivity, 1991 (Box BB2)
      - Kids' market-menu census, noodle soup vs. competition, 1991 (Box BB2)
      - Knowledge-Based Marketing Analysis for Tomato, Chicken Noodle and Cream of Mushroom Condensed Soups, 1992, (2 folders) (Box BB2)
      - Management Communications Conference, 1989-1990 (Box BB2)
      - Market structure audit, 1987, (1 of 2 folders) (Box BB2)
      - Market structure audit, 1987, (2 of 2 folders) (Box BB3)
      - Maximizing Our Market, 1986 (Box BB3)
      - Miscellaneous research, 1990-1992 (Box BB3)
      - Presentation of a Quantitative Positioning Study for Campbell's New Dry Regular Soups, undated (Box BB3)
      - Primary demand strategy, 1992 (Box BB3)
      - Product Value Analysis of Three Campbell's Red & White Label Soups, 1990 (Box BB3)
      - Proposal for More Effective Marketing of Campbell's Soups, 1991 (Box BB3)
      - Proposal for Umbrella Marketing for the Soup Business, 1986 (Box BB3)
      - Proposed New Product Research Program, 1977 (Box BB3)
      - Red & White Condensed Soup Strategy Study, 1989 (Box BB3)
      - Red & white soup core creative strategies, 1990 (Box BB3)
      - Red & white soup historical media plans 1980-1989, 1990 (Box BB3)
      - Red & white soup search for effective strategy, 1990 (Box BB3)
      - Red & white soup status update, 1991 (Box BB4)
      - Red & white soup variety usage, 1992 (Box BB4)
      - Red & white vegetable soup revitalization plan, 1991 (Box BB4)
      - Sales data, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Situation analysis, 1980 (Box BB4)
      - Soup 101, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Soup creative summit, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Soup usage dynamics, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Spending, 1991 (Box BB4)
      - Storyboards, undated (Box BB4)
      - Strategic exploration, 1989 (Box BB4)
      - Strategy studies, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Tomato soup, 1990-1991 (Box BB4)
      - Umbrella and red & white strategic review, 1986 (Box BB4)
      - Where the Action Is in Food Marketing, 1992 (Box BB4)
      - Worldwide Marketing Seminar, 1990 (Box BB4)
      - Worldwide Soup Symposium, 1991 (Box BB5)
    - Compuserve
      - Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box BB5)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box BB5)
      - Letters of agreement, 1990 (Box BB5)
      - Pricing, 1990-1992 (Box BB5)
      - Review of Compuserve's pricing policies, 1990 (Box BB5)
      - Slides, undated (Box BB5)
    - Dentsu
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1988-1992 (Box BB5)
    - Hyundai
      - Confidential analysis on managing the numbers for profit, 1992 (Box BB5)
      - Contracts, 1985-1992 (Box BB5)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1992 and undated (Box BB5)
    - Kal-Kan
      - Advertising spending, 1990 (Box BB5)
      - Compensation agreement, 1989 (Box BB6)
    - M&M/Mars
      - Advertising agency compensation, 1990 (Box BB6)
      - Five Principles of Mars, 1983 (Box BB6)
      - Post-Olympic copy brief, 1992 (Box BB6)
    - Maybelline
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1990-1991 and undated (Box BB6)
      - Market for toiletries and cosmetics in the U.S., 1989 (Box BB6)
      - Media Delivery Can Make a Difference, undated (Box BB6)
      - Presentation, 1987 (Box BB6)
      - Print advertising and storyboards, 1983-1990 and undated (Box BB6)
      - Retail environment, undated (Box BB6)
      - Trends Affecting the Cosmetics Business, undated (Box BB6)
      - World of Women and Cosmetics, undated (Box BB6)
    - Miller Brewing Company
      - 1994 Beer industry update, 1994 (Box BB6)
      - Assessment of Miller High Life marketing situation 1972-1983, 1984 (Box BB6)
      - Beer--Additional Data, 1991 (Box BB6)
      - Beer--An Overview, 1991 (Box BB6)
      - Beer Industry Consolidation Analysis, 1991 (Box BB7)
      - Brand dynamics, 1991 (Box BB7)
      - Beer market structure, 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box BB7)
      - Brand image and market structure, 1992 (Box BB7)
      - brand image data, 1991 (Box BB7)
      - Branded food and beverage presentation, 1991 (Box BB7)
      - Cambridge consumer-based market structure study, 1990 (Box BB7)
      - Clippings, 1991-1995, (2 folders) (Box BB7)
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1990-1994 and undated, (2 folders) (Box BB8)
      - Demographics, 1991 (Box BB8)
      - Enhancing MBC's Competitive Performance in a Share Marketing Environment, 1994, (2 folders) (Box BB8)
      - Ice beer research review, 1994 (Box BB8)
      - Ice category, 1994 (Box BB8)
      - Management seminar, 1992 (Box BB8)
      - Miller Ad Effectiveness Study, 1992 (Box BB8)
      - Miller Genuine Draft/Light Franchise Synergy Analysis, 1991 (Box BB8)
      - Miller Lite Ice, undated (Box BB8)
      - Miller trademark management, 1995 (Box BB8)
      - Opportunities with Drinkers Age 35+, 1991 (Box BB8)
      - Pricing, 1991 (Box BB9)
      - Research, 1991-1992 and undated (Box BB9)
      - Transformation of the Packaged Food and Beverage Marketing Environment and Its Impact on Marketing Communications, 1991 (Box BB9)
      - United States Beer Industry, Miller Genuine Draft/Light and Millerness, 1991 (Box BB9)
      - U.S. beer market, Impact Databank review and forecast, 1993, (2 folders) (Box BB9)
      - Year-end update, 1994 (Box BB9)
    - MTA (Metropolitan Transit Authority)
      - Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box BB9)
      - Consumer Decision Criteria Study, undated (Box BB9)